Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
6199/009 mf
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE); HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Office
71 microfilm reels
Reports, correspondence, microfilm.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
7.89 cubic feet
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE); HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Office
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. LEGAL FILES (ATTORNEYS - 1973-1978).
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. - Miscellaneous.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Correspondence.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Files. Ero Records Through 1984.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1981-1982.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1983-1987.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1988-1990.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1991.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1992-1993.
Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. LEGAL FILES (ATTORNEYS - 1973-1978)
  - Ahern & Gillogly, Ltd. Correspondence., 1976-1977; 1 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00002 on Files reel 1.
  - Bodle, Fogel, Julber, Reinhardt & Rothschild, Los Angeles, CA. Correspondence., 1974-1977; 2 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00398 on Files reel 1.
  - Bodle, Fogel, Julber, Reinhardt & Rothschild, Los Angeles, CA. Correspondence., 1978-1979; 3 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00547 on Files reel 1.
  - Davis, Cowell & Bowe, San Francisco, CA., 1977-1978; 4 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00670 on Files reel 1.
  - Girardi, Keese & Crane, Los Angeles, CA., 1977-1980; 5 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00753 on Files reel 1.
  - Josephson & Trickey, Anchorage, AK., 1978-1980; 6 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00795 on Files reel 1.
  - Mamber, Epstein & Elster., 1978-1979; 7 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00821 on Files reel 1.
  - Katz, Jonas B. Correspondence., 1973-1975; 8 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 00842 on Files reel 1.
  - Katz, Jonas B. Correspondence., 1976-1977; 9 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01045 on Files reel 1.
  - Katz, Jonas B. Correspondence., 1978; 10 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01232 on Files reel 1.
  - Linehan, Edward T. Correspondence., 1973-1977; 11 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01339 on Files reel 1.
  - Mozer & Gulmi, New York, NY. Correspondence., 1973-1976; 12 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01498 on Files reel 1.
  - Mozer & Gulmi, New York, NY. Correspondence., 1977-1978; 13 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01726 on Files reel 1.
  - Reynolds, John J., General Counesl. Correspondence., 1973-1974; 14 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 01892 on Files reel 1.
  - Reynolds, John J., General Counesl. Correspondence., 1975; 15 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 02076 on Files reel 1.
  - Reynolds, John J., General Counesl. Correspondence., 1976; 16 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 02227 on Files reel 1.
  - Reynolds, John J., General Counesl. Correspondence., 1977-1978; 17 (Reel 1)
    Beginning at frame 02541 on Files reel 1.
  - Reynolds, John J., Chicago, IL., 1979; 1 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00002 on Files reel 2.
  - Rice, Hoppner & Hedland, Chicago, IL., 1978-1979; 2 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00032 on Files reel 2.
  - Smith, Kircher, Cincinnati, OH., 1974-1977; 3 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00340 on Files reel 2.
  - Venn, Jerry Frederick, Cincinnati, OH, 1972-1976; 4 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00455 on Files reel 2.
  - Villalta, V. A., Calistoga, CA., 1978; 5 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00514 on Files reel 2.
  - Walsh, Carl M., Chicago, IL, 1974-1977; 6 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00517 on Files reel 2.
  - Winston & Strawn, Washington, DC., 1974-1975; 7 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00586 on Files reel 2.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. - Miscellaneous.
  - Aircraft. Bills, 1975-1976; 8 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00609 on Files reel 2.
  - Aircraft. Bills, 1977-1979; 9 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 00772 on Files reel 2.
  - Aircraft. Bills, 1975-1979; 10 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01088 on Files reel 2.
  - Aircraft. Taxes and Yearly Ohio Aircraft Registration., 1977-1980; 11 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01499 on Files reel 2.
  - American Arbitration Assocation., 1976-1983; 12 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01542 on Files reel 2.
  - American Express Co., 1976-1983; 13 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01546 on Files reel 2.
  - Bastian Bros. Co., 1976-1982; 14 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01601 on Files reel 2.
  - Burroughs Corp., 1978-1980; 15 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01625 on Files reel 2.
  - Canadian Motor Vehicle, 1976-1981; 16 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01660 on Files reel 2.
  - Car Leases & Rentals., 1976-1977; 17 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01694 on Files reel 2.
  - Car Leases & Rentals., 1978-1979; 18 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 01933 on Files reel 2.
  - Car Leases & Rentals., 1980-1982; 19 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 02301 on Files reel 2.
  - Catering Industry Employee. Correspondence., 1972-1976; 20 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 02602 on Files reel 2.
  - Catering Industry Employee., 1977; 21 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 02752 on Files reel 2.
  - Catering Industry Employee., 1978-1979; 22 (Reel 2)
    Beginning at frame 02918 on Files reel 2.
  - Cincinnati Bell Telephone., 1976-1979; 1 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00002 on Files reel 3.
  - Condo, Washington, DC., 1980-1983; 2 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00224 on Files reel 3.
  - Cosell's "Day With the All-Americans.", 1979-1982; 3 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00354 on Files reel 3.
  - Crocker National Bank. Special Account., 1981-1982; 4 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00445 on Files reel 3.
  - Walter P. Dole (Insurance), Earl Conklin, Agent., 1976-1981; 5 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00491 on Files reel 3.
  - Educational Conference. Health, Welfare & Pension Plans, Inc., 1977-1980; 6 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00650 on Files reel 3.
  - First National Bank of Cincinnati. Atlas Office., 1962-1979; 7 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00669 on Files reel 3.
  - First National Bank of Cincinnati., 1980-1982; 8 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00780 on Files reel 3.
  - Form Letters and Miscellaneous., 1973-1982; 9 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 00998 on Files reel 3.
  - Give Away Items., 1976-1982; 10 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01474 on Files reel 3.
  - Bob Hope Supershow., 1978; 11 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01488 on Files reel 3.
  - International Labor Press Association., 1982; 12 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01491 on Files reel 3.
  - Investments. Bank., 1974-1982; 13 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01494 on Files reel 3.
  - Investments. Miscellaneous., 1971-1981; 14 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01739 on Files reel 3.
  - Investments. Randolph Building., 1982; 15 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01741 on Files reel 3.
  - Juliano, Robert E. Legislative Representative., 1973-1982; 16 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01758 on Files reel 3.
  - Keeler/Morris, Larry McVey. Printing., 1966-1976; 17 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01905 on Files reel 3.
  - Kelly Press., 1977-1979; 18 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 01962 on Files reel 3.
  - Lavin, John P., 1975-1981; 19 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02012 on Files reel 3.
  - Leasco., 1973-1977; 20 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02055 on Files reel 3.
  - Leefe, Donald., 1976; 21 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02184 on Files reel 3.
  - Marquardt, B. V., Printing Co., 1976-1982; 22 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02190 on Files reel 3.
  - Metro Computing, Inc., 1978-1981; 23 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02254 on Files reel 3.
  - Meyers, William L., Inc., 1976-1981; 24 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02278 on Files reel 3.
  - Microfilm Bids., 1982; 25 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02319 on Files reel 3.
  - Microfilm Equipment., 1976-1981; 26 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02325 on Files reel 3.
  - National Co-Ordinating Committee for Multi-Employer Plans., 1975-1981; 27 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02345 on Files reel 3.
  - New York-Hotel Motel Trades Council., 1974-1979; 28 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02475 on Files reel 3.
  - O.P.E.I.U. Local 99, 1974-1982; 29 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02507 on Files reel 3.
  - Palm Springs. John Floyd., 1975-1977; 30 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02563 on Files reel 3.
  - Palm Springs. Harel Associates., 1978-1981; 31 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02571 on Files reel 3.
  - Palm Springs. Miscellaneous., 1976-1980; 32 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02582 on Files reel 3.
  - Race Track Advisory Council., 1976-1980; 33 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02610 on Files reel 3.
  - Randolph, Philip A. Institute., 1976-1981; 34 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02635 on Files reel 3.
  - Roessler Brothers., 1973-1984; 35 (Reel 3)
    Beginning at frame 02654 on Files reel 3.
  - Royal Bank of Canada., 1974-1982; 1 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00002 on Files reel 4.
  - Simonds, George A. and Co., Inc. (Bookbinders)., 1956-1977; 2 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00299 on Files reel 4.
  - TIP Correspondence., 1977-1982; 3 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00331 on Files reel 4.
  - Thomas E. Wood Agency (Earl Conklin, Agent)., 1980-1981; 4 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00614 on Files reel 4.
  - Xerox Company., 1963-1977; 5 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00672 on Files reel 4.
  - 50 Year Pins., 1961-1981; 6 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 00815 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. EBS-1 Reports., 1977; 7 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 01560 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Old U.S. Department of Labor Filing., 1973-1976; 8 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 01575 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Perspective Magazine., 1976-1977; 9 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 01743 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Premiums., 1975-1979; 10 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 01947 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Correspondence., 1976-1980; 11 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02227 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Summary Annual Reports., 1980; 12 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02280 on Files reel 4.
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield. Summary Plan Description., 1977-1978; 13 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02289 on Files reel 4.
  - Pension Benefit Guaranty Corp., 1977-1980; 14 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02390 on Files reel 4.
  - EBS-1 Filings for International Death Burial Benefit Fund., 1974-1978; 15 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02538 on Files reel 4.
  - H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Linda O'Neill (memberships), 1978; 16 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02611 on Files reel 4.
  - H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Linda O'Neill (memberships), 1978; 17 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 02851 on Files reel 4.
  - H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Linda O'Neill (memberships), 1979; 18 (Reel 4)
    Beginning at frame 03188 on Files reel 4.
  - H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Linda O'Neill (memberships), 1979; 1 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00002 on Files reel 5.
  - H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Linda O'Neill (memberships), 1979; 2 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00113 on Files reel 5.
  - Officers & Employees of Locals. H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund. Yearly Audit Reports., 1977-1981; 3 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00345 on Files reel 5.
  - Continental Plan for Local Union Officers., 1977; 4 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00434 on Files reel 5.
  - Continental Plan for Local Union Officers., 1978-1979; 5 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00720 on Files reel 5.
  - Officers & Employees of Locals. H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund., 1976-1977; 6 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 00815 on Files reel 5.
  - Officers & Employees of Locals. H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund., 1978; 7 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 01002 on Files reel 5.
  - Officers & Employees of Locals. H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund., 1979; 8 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 01161 on Files reel 5.
  - Officers & Employees of Locals. H. &. R.E. & B.I.U. Pension Fund., 1980; 9 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 01467 on Files reel 5.
  - Continental Plan for Local Union Officers. Canadian Filing Information., 1961-1966; 10 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 01713 on Files reel 5.
  - International Funds., 1976-1977; 11 (Reel 5)
    Beginning at frame 01959 on Files reel 5.
  - Culinary Institute of America., 1 (Reel 6)
    Beginning at frame 00003 on Files reel 6.
  - Culinary Institute of America. By-Laws., 1962-1972; 2 (Reel 6)
    Beginning at frame 00004 on Files reel 6.
  - Culinary Institute of America. Correspondence., 1960-1976; 3 (Reel 6)
    Beginning at frame 00065 on Files reel 6.
  - Culinary Institute of America. Miscellaneous., 1968-1977; 4 (Reel 6)
    Beginning at frame 00879 on Files reel 6.
  - Barmaid File., 1950-1956; 1 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 7.
  - Bastian Bros. Co., 1965-1975; 2 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 00127 on Files reel 7.
  - Catering Industry Employee., 1980-1981; 3 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 00461 on Files reel 7.
  - Buxton & Skinner. Larry McVey., 4 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 00996 on Files reel 7.
  - Congratulatory Messages. Robert Diefenbach., 1963; 5 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01015 on Files reel 7.
  - Congratulatory Messages. J. Gieson., 1973-1974; 6 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01193 on Files reel 7.
  - Gibson, John F. Personal File., 1968-1977; 7 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01240 on Files reel 7.
  - Cooper, John. File., 1962; 8 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01434 on Files reel 7.
  - Democratic Committee Contributions., 1960-1962; 9 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01470 on Files reel 7.
  - Exposition Press, Inc., 1961-1963; 10 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01500 on Files reel 7.
  - Kelly Press. Correspondence., 1980-1981; 11 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 01571 on Files reel 7.
  - Merkle Press. Correspondence., 1958; 12 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 02099 on Files reel 7.
  - Merkle Press. Correspondence., 1965; 13 (Reel 7)
    Beginning at frame 02349 on Files reel 7.
  - Merkle Press. Correspondence., 1965-1979; 1 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 8.
  - Merkle Press. Statements of Ownership., 1962-1976; 2 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 00433 on Files reel 8.
  - Miller, Ed. S. Confidential., 1958-1982; 3 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 00719 on Files reel 8.
  - Registration. Insignia and Trademark., 1930-1981; 4 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 00753 on Files reel 8.
  - Registration. Label. By State., 1954-1972; 5 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 00902 on Files reel 8.
  - Roessler Brothers. Correspondence., 1966; 6 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 01241 on Files reel 8.
  - Secretaries Handbook., 7 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 01619 on Files reel 8.
  - Mr. Wasson. Sample Correspondence., 1952-1962; 8 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 01681 on Files reel 8.
  - Health and Welfare Questionnaries. Correspondence., 1957-1974; 9 (Reel 8)
    Beginning at frame 01757 on Files reel 8.
  - Health and Welfare Questionnaries. Correspondence., 1957-1974; 1 (Reel 9)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 9.
  - Health and Welfare Questionnaries. Correspondence., 1957-1974; 2 (Reel 9)
    Beginning at frame 02118 on Files reel 9.
  - Letter Listing., 1973-1980; 1 (Reel 10)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 10.
  - Letter Listing., 1981-1983; 2 (Reel 10)
    Beginning at frame 00710 on Files reel 10.
  - Death Claim Receipts Returned., 1971-1982; 3 (Reel 10)
    Beginning at frame 01245 on Files reel 10.
  - Catering Industry Employee in Memoriam., 1971-1976; 4 (Reel 10)
    Beginning at frame 01270 on Files reel 10.
  - Catering Industry Employee in Memoriam., 1976; 1 (Reel 11)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 11.
  - Shortage Information. Correspondence with U.S.F.&G., 1942-1978; 2 (Reel 11)
    Beginning at frame 00938 on Files reel 11.
  - U.S.F.&G. Bonding Records., 1961-1981; 3 (Reel 11)
    Beginning at frame 01103 on Files reel 11.
  - Bond Record Books., 1971-1981; 4 (Reel 11)
    Beginning at frame 01602 on Files reel 11.
  - American Airlines Credit Cards., 1968-1982; 5 (Reel 11)
    Beginning at frame 01925 on Files reel 11.
  - Air Travel Cards Returned., 1974-1980; 1 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 12.
  - Office Employees. Contracts., 1957-1976; 2 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 00124 on Files reel 12.
  - Employees. Payroll Records., 1955-1972; 3 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 00530 on Files reel 12.
  - Employees. Vacations., 1962-1982; 4 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 00824 on Files reel 12.
  - Employees. Attendance Record., 1980-1982; 5 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 01523 on Files reel 12.
  - Employees. Vacations., 1983; 6 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 01609 on Files reel 12.
  - Employees. Vacations., 1984; 7 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 01767 on Files reel 12.
  - TIP Fund. Staff Contributions., 1977-1983; 8 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 01935 on Files reel 12.
  - Audits Received form Lester Green, International Vice-President., 1968-1980; 9 (Reel 12)
    Beginning at frame 02356 on Files reel 12.
  - Hanson, Vernard H., International Auditor. Audits Received and Commissions., 1965-1983; 1 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 13.
  - Hanson, Vernard H., International Auditor. Correspondence., 1983; 2 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00202 on Files reel 13.
  - Klayman, Hyman G., International Auditor. Audits Received and Commissions., 1968-1984; 3 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00226 on Files reel 13.
  - Klayman, Hyman G., International Auditor. Correspondence., 1983-1984; 4 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00425 on Files reel 13.
  - Richard, Richard A., International Auditor. Audits Received and Commissions., 1983-1984; 5 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00670 on Files reel 13.
  - Richard, Richard A., International Auditor. Correspondence., 1983-1984; 6 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00676 on Files reel 13.
  - Insurance Policy and Corrspondence. International Auditors Equipment., 1967-1970; 7 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00762 on Files reel 13.
  - Claims Filed for Lost Adding Machines and Typewriters., 1964-1968; 8 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00789 on Files reel 13.
  - Welfare/Pension Trust. Minutes., 1981-1983; 9 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 00841 on Files reel 13.
  - Welfare/Pension Fund. Appeals., 1981; 10 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 01514 on Files reel 13.
  - Welfare/Pension Fund. Appeals., 1983; 11 (Reel 13)
    Beginning at frame 01944 on Files reel 13.
  - Welfare/Pension Fund. Appeals., 1983; 1 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 14.
  - Welfare/Pension Fund. Appeals Committee., 1983; 2 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 00898 on Files reel 14.
  - International Pension Plan. Copy, 1949; 3 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 01409 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension. Correspondence., 1952-1958; 4 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 01450 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension/Welfare Disclosure Act., 1958-1960; 5 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 01642 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension. Department of Labor Filing., 1959; 6 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 01751 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension Fund. Reports., 1960-1969; 7 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 01785 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension Fund. Reports., 1957-1959; 8 (Reel 14)
    Beginning at frame 02032 on Files reel 14.
  - Pension Fund. Reports., 1907-1974; 1 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 15.
  - Pension Plan., 1975; 2 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00402 on Files reel 15.
  - Pension Plan., 1976; 3 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00645 on Files reel 15.
  - Pension Plan., 1977; 4 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00768 on Files reel 15.
  - Group Insurance. Application and Correspondence., 1977-1978; 5 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00789 on Files reel 15.
  - International Employees Insurance Policy Numbers., 1966-1978; 6 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00895 on Files reel 15.
  - Tedtmann, M. Earl, CPA. Correspondence., 1966-1977; 7 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00926 on Files reel 15.
  - Accountant's Report. C.O.P.E. Fund., 1964-1966; 8 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00987 on Files reel 15.
  - Finances for Reference., 1964-1972; 9 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 00996 on Files reel 15.
  - Quarterly International Financial Statement. M. Earl Tedtmann., 1955-1976; 10 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 01319 on Files reel 15.
  - Accountant's Reports. M. Earl Tedtmann. I.U. Year End., 1955-1976; 11 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 01382 on Files reel 15.
  - Accountant's Reports. Thomas W. Havey & Co. I.U. Year End., 1977-1981; 12 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 01671 on Files reel 15.
  - Board Prop. Appropriations., 1963-1973; 13 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 02052 on Files reel 15.
  - General Executive Board (GEB). Minutes., 1947-1959; 14 (Reel 15)
    Beginning at frame 02211 on Files reel 15.
  - General Executive Board (GEB). Minutes., 1960-1969; 1 (Reel 16)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 16.
  - General Executive Board (GEB). Minutes., 1970-1979; 2 (Reel 16)
    Beginning at frame 00495 on Files reel 16.
  - Convention Files., 1961; 3 (Reel 16)
    Beginning at frame 01631 on Files reel 16.
  - Convention Files., 1966; 4 (Reel 16)
    Beginning at frame 01760 on Files reel 16.
  - Convention Files. Miscellaneous., 1966; 1 (Reel 17)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 17.
  - Convention Files., 1971; 2 (Reel 17)
    Beginning at frame 00105 on Files reel 17.
  - Special Convention., 1974; 3 (Reel 17)
    Beginning at frame 00999 on Files reel 17.
  - Special Convention. (continued)., 1974; 1 (Reel 18)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 18.
  - Convention Files., 1976; 2 (Reel 18)
    Beginning at frame 00458 on Files reel 18.
  - Convention Files., 1981; 3 (Reel 18)
    Beginning at frame 01393 on Files reel 18.
  - Culinary Institute of America. General Correspondence., 1980-1984; 4 (Reel 18)
    Beginning at frame 01506 on Files reel 18.
  - Culinary Institute of America. Trustees Correspondence., 1980-1982; 1 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 19.
  - Scholarships. Miscellaneous Correspondence., 1981-9183; 2 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 00507 on Files reel 19.
  - National Cooking Institute., 1979; 3 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 00888 on Files reel 19.
  - Eastern Regional Office., 1973-1979; 4 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 01090 on Files reel 19.
  - Eastern Regional Office. Correspondence., 1980-1984; 5 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 02167 on Files reel 19.
  - Reply Message., 1981; 6 (Reel 19)
    Beginning at frame 02451 on Files reel 19.
  - Eastern Regional Office. Correspondence. (continued)., 1980-1984; 1 (Reel 20)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 20.
  - Eastern Regional Office. Insurance and Pension., 1977-1983; 2 (Reel 20)
    Beginning at frame 00325 on Files reel 20.
  - Western Regional Office. Correspondence., 1974-1979; 3 (Reel 20)
    Beginning at frame 00525 on Files reel 20.
  - Western Regional Office. Insurance and Pension., 1977-1983; 4 (Reel 20)
    Beginning at frame 00883 on Files reel 20.
  - Western Regional Office. Correspondence., 1980-1984; 5 (Reel 20)
    Beginning at frame 01217 on Files reel 20.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Correspondence.